Mary Mitchell P015 P015
Stage
- Series 1
  - US Supreme Court (Box 1, Folder 80)
    - US Supreme Court, undated (Item 1)
      House (unknown location)
    - US Supreme Court, undated (Item 2)
      View of East Pediment from Terrace Court
    - US Supreme Court, undated (Item 3)
    - US Supreme Court, undated (Item 4)
  - Law House – 1252 6th Street, SW (Box 1, Folder 81)
    - Law House – 1252 6th Street, SW, undated (Item 1)
      People on swings in park across from Thomas Law House
    - Law House – 1252 6th Street, SW, undated (Item 2)
      Children on slide across from Thomas Law House
    - Law House – 1252 6th Street, SW, undated (Item 3)
    - Law House – 1252 6th Street, SW, undated (Item 4)
      Thomas Law house and park with playground
  - Washington Navy Yard (Box 1, Folder 82)
    - Washington Navy Yard, undated (Item 1)
      Tennis Courts near penitentiary on Fort McNair
    - Washington Navy Yard, undated (Item 2)
      Cannons in Leutze Park, Washington Navy Yard
    - Washington Navy Yard, undated (Item 3)
    - Washington Navy Yard, undated (Item 4)
  - Washington Navy Yard (Box 1, Folder 83)
    - Washington Navy Yard, undated (Item 1)
      Officers Quarters – Fort McNair
    - Washington Navy Yard, undated (Item 2)
    - Washington Navy Yard, undated (Item 3)
    - Washington Navy Yard, undated (Item 4)
  - Southwest Washington (Box 1, Folder 84)
    - Southwest Washington, undated (Item 1)
      Apartment house
    - Southwest Washington, undated (Item 2)
      House in Southwest
    - Southwest Washington, undated (Item 3)
    - Southwest Washington, undated (Item 4)
  - Carrolsburg Place (Box 1, Folder 85)
    - Carrolsburg Place, undated (Item 1)
      Houses along Carrolsburg Place
    - Carrolsburg Place, undated (Item 2)
    - Carrolsburg Place, undated (Item 3)
    - Carrolsburg Place, undated (Item 4)
  - Renwick Gallery (Pennsylvania Avenue) (Box 1, Folder 86)
    - Renwick Gallery (Pennsylvania Avenue), undated (Item 1)
      View of Renwick Gallery from Eisenhower Executive Office Building
    - Renwick Gallery (Pennsylvania Avenue), undated (Item 2)
    - Renwick Gallery (Pennsylvania Avenue), undated (Item 3)
    - Renwick Gallery (Pennsylvania Avenue), undated (Item 4)
      People standing on street near Renwick Gallery
  - Decatur House (Box 1, Folder 87)
    - Decatur House, undated (Item 1)
      View of Decatur House from Lafayette Park
    - Decatur House, undated (Item 2)
    - Decatur House, undated (Item 3)
    - Decatur House, undated (Item 4)
      Children playing at Lincoln Memorial
  - Corcoran Gallery of Art (Box 1, Folder 88)
    - Corcoran Gallery of Art, undated (Item 1)
      Lion outside the Corcoran with Eisenhower Executive Office Building in background
    - Corcoran Gallery of Art, undated (Item 2)
    - Corcoran Gallery of Art, undated (Item 3)
    - Corcoran Gallery of Art, undated (Item 4)
  - Lafayette Park (Box 1, Folder 89)
    - Lafayette Park, undated (Item 1)
      President Andrew Jackson statue
    - Lafayette Park, undated (Item 2)
    - Lafayette Park, undated (Item 3)
    - Lafayette Park, undated (Item 4)
  - National Cathedral (Box 1, Folder 90)
    - National Cathedral, undated (Item 1)
      Steps and iron handrail
    - National Cathedral, undated (Item 2)
      National Cathedral through the trees
    - National Cathedral, undated (Item 3)
    - National Cathedral, undated (Item 4)
      George Washington statue at National Cathedral
  - Peterson House (Box 1, Folder 91)
    - Peterson House, undated (Item 1)
      Peterson House, taken from Ford's Theatre
    - Peterson House, undated (Item 2)
    - Peterson House, undated (Item 3)
    - Peterson House, undated (Item 4)
      Julius Garfinckel and Company store
  - Ford's Theatre (Box 1, Folder 92)
    - Ford's Theatre, undated (Item 1)
      Lincoln's presidential box
    - Ford's Theatre, undated (Item 2)
    - Ford's Theatre, undated (Item 3)
    - Ford's Theatre, undated (Item 4)
  - Madison House (Box 1, Folder 93)
    - Madison House, undated (Item 1)
      Dolly Madison House taken from Lafayette Park
    - Madison House, undated (Item 2)
    - Madison House, undated (Item 3)
      People in Lafayette Park
    - Madison House, undated (Item 4)
      People walking in Lafayette Park
  - Washington Statue (Box 1, Folder 94)
    - Washington Statue, undated (Item 1)
      Horatio Greenough's sculpture of George Washington
    - Washington Statue, undated (Item 2)
    - Washington Statue, undated (Item 3)
      Elephant in Smithsonian Museum of Natural History
    - Washington Statue, undated (Item 4)
      Smithsonian Museum of Natural History
  - Benjamin Franklin Statue (Box 1, Folder 95)
    - Benjamin Franklin Statue, undated (Item 1)
      People walking past south side of the White House
    - Benjamin Franklin Statue, undated (Item 2)
      Benjamin Franklin statue – Old Post Office Building
    - Benjamin Franklin Statue, undated (Item 3)
    - Benjamin Franklin Statue, undated (Item 4)
  - Colder Sculpture (Box 1, Folder 96)
    - Colder Sculpture, undated (Item 1)
      Alexander Colder sculpture at Smithsonian Museum
    - Colder Sculpture, undated (Item 2)
    - Colder Sculpture, undated (Item 3)
    - Colder Sculpture, undated (Item 4)
  - Octagon House (Box 1, Folder 97)
    - Octagon House, undated (Item 1)
      Table on which President James Madison signed the Treaty of Ghent in 1815
    - Octagon House, undated (Item 2)
    - Octagon House, undated (Item 3)
    - Octagon House, undated (Item 4)
    - Octagon House, undated (Item 5)
    - Octagon House, undated (Item 6)
    - Octagon House, undated (Item 7)